Hi, my name is Jessica Claire, and I'm a dating coach for New York Dating Coach, and we're here in New York City.
Clue number one, she's looking at you.
Not just at your eyes, or your face, but at your body.
Women almost always go about what they're interested in, so if she's giving you a couple of looks, that's a good indicator.
Secondly, she'll position herself nearest to you.
If you're in a bar or a club, guaranteed she will have touched you, if she's interested in you.
Whether it be your arm, or your leg, a girl almost always makes contact with someone that she's interested in.
Secondly, she'll lean in, or show herself off.
She might open her arms wider, or touch her hair, or touch her body, or her face.
Either way, if she's touching herself, and she's close to you, it's almost always true that she's interested.
How to know if she's not interested?
She'll walk away.
She'll close herself off, and she won't look at you.
This is Jessica Claire, with New York Dating Coach, and this has been, how to know if a girl likes you.